MARIAH KEY

512-496-9323 mariahdkey@gmail.com

5604 Southwest Pkwy Austin, TX, 78735

Behance

Portfolio Website

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Skills:

- User Research
- · Competitive Analysis
- User Interviews
- User Personas
- Wireframing: Low, Mid and High-Fidelity
- Prototyping
- Frontend
 Development

Tools:

- Adobe XD
- Figma
- · Usability Hub
- Photoshop
- CSS, JavaScript and HTML
- · Microsoft Office
- Google Suites

PROFILE

UI Designer with a background in art and customer service. Ability to create functional and aesthetic designs. Experience working with clients and vendors utilizing time management and organizational skills. Open to working a remote position.

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry

Certificate in UI Design with a Specialization in Frontend Development, 2024

Texas State University, San Marcos, TX

Bachelor of Fine Art in Art and Art History, 2019

EXPERIENCE

Mobile Phlebotomy Customer Experience Associate;

Austin, TX — 2021 - Present

- Coordinating scheduling of patients through communication with vendors and physicians within the desired time range.
- Assisting in exceeding the company goal of scheduling over 50,000 mobile blood draws within the Women's Health, Oncology and Organ Health departments.

Store Support, Whole Foods Market;

Austin, TX — 2020 - 2021

- Created a positive customer experience while demonstrating product knowledge and communicating the company's sustainability goals.
- Trained and supported team members in standard operating procedures and expectations for customer service.

Server and Bartender with Marketing Position, First Watch;

Cedar Park, TX — 2019 - 2020

- Trained on average 3 new team members a week.
- Held a marketing position and attended events speaking to the community about the company's farm to market values.

Head Host, The Oasis on Lake Travis;

Austin, TX — 2016 - 2018

- Worked to exceed expectations for thousands of guests weekly at one of Austin's largest tourist attractions.
- Set expectations and supported new hires through training.
- · Provided service to private events.